earthfiles.com 2018-09-05

# Privacy Policy – Earthfiles

This document explains Earthfiles.com’s (“Earthfiles”) policies for the collection, use and disclosure of personal information. This policy forms part of, and should be read in conjunction with, our  **Terms and Conditions.**

Earthfiles believes that privacy is crucial for the ongoing success of Internet commerce. Your use of this Earthfiles.com website constitutes acceptance of these terms and conditions. If you do not agree with these policies, please cease using this site immediately. Earthfiles reserves the right to make amendments to this Privacy Policy from time to time.

**Sharing of Information:**

Certain information provided to Earthfiles in the Subscription Sign Up or Earthfiles Shop Merchant Account is shared only with other parties necessary to complete transactions, such as PayPal, its consultants and professional advisers on PayPal’s behalf for the uses disclosed herein. Earthfiles does not share personal information with any other third parties.

**Server Logs:**

The web server does log your IP address in standard server logs. We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer Earthfiles.

**Contact Us/Email Inquiries:**

No information sent to Earthfiles via email or Earthfile’s Subscription Sign Up form is used for any other reason than to respond to and maintain a record of the inquiry. This information is not sent to third parties or retained for mailing list purposes, other than Earthfiles’ own list of subscribers and Earthfiles Shop purchasers in order to maintain log records of all transactions.

**Cookies:**

If you are a member, Earthfiles uses cookies to remember you so you don’t have to re-enter each time you change among Earthfiles report pages.

**Ads:**

Ads appearing on the site may be delivered to users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by Eathfiles and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

**Information You Provide to Us:  
**  
It’s probably no surprise that we collect information that you provide to us. The amount and type of information depends on the context and how we use the information. Here are some examples:

**Basic Account Information:  **We ask for basic information from you in order to set up your account. For example, we require individuals who sign up for an account to provide a username and email address. You may provide us with more information – like your name – but we don’t require that information to create an account.

**Transaction and Billing Information:  **If you buy something from us – a subscription plan, a book or DVD, for example – you will provide additional personal and payment information that is required to process the transaction and your payment, such as your name, credit card information, and contact information.

**Communications With Us** : You may also provide us information when you communicate with our support team, or email to ask a question or share your experiences.
